Amanda Seals here joined by co-founder and managing partner of the Fearless Fund and
Fearless Foundation, Arian Simone. The Fearless Fund has been out here making it possible for
Black women entrepreneurs to grow their businesses and their visions and is also the target of a
current court case led by Edward Bloom who led the charge to get rid of affirmative action and
they are now he is now leading the charge to undermine the work of the Fearless Fund in the
hopes of making it illegal for Black folks to be able to help other Black folks through you know
practices, foundations, organizations that are targeted towards us specifically. I want to really
just give some attention right now to just telling people not just what the Fearless Fund is but what
y'all have done. We have deployed over 27 million dollars in investment capital to Black and brown
women. We have awarded over 400 grants to Black and brown women's businesses. We have educated over
a thousand women of color founders every year. How can we prioritize supporting the Fearless Fund and
championing economic justice and social justice? One, share this on all your social media handles.
People need to be aware of this case because it affects you. Two, you can sign a petition at
fearlessfreedomnow.org or you can donate to our foundation right on our website. You can go to
fearless.fund, click on foundation and make a donation to this work that we do.